techrobo.org 2015-04-16

# Privacy Policy | Tech Robo

**Privacy Policy for www.techrobo.org**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin@techrobo.org

At www.techrobo.org, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.techrobo.org and how it is used.

**Visitors details**

Techrobo.org uses Google Analytics for collecting visitors details. Google Analytics helps us to find all information regarding our website such as page views, unique visitors’ details, visitors location and so on. Thanks to Google for helping Webmasters. We also use a third party company to get more details

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.techrobo.org makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes Internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

www.techrobo.org does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Ad Policy**

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site to serve their ads on this blog.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**User Comments**

Techrobo.org  allows users to comment on the site. However we hold all rights to accept or reject any comments based on our discretion.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Policy Change Information:-**

Techrobo.org can change this privacy policy any time for their own private reason. You are requested to check our privacy policy in every weeks.

Last Update:- 06 June, 2014.
